FIVE DAYS AGO
Father, I can sense Demons
in this town as well.
Yes... I can smell them.
Keisuke, over here!
Is it a Demon, Father?!
I've located a lady!
Father!!
Keisuke, go somewhere
for a little bit!
No, we need to
track down the Demons!
Please, Keisuke, please!
Eek! You're scaring me!
N-No!
Hey Missy,
let's have some fun!
We need to help her!
Wait!
We could y'know,
do this... or that...
Let's have fun!
What? A human?
Huh?
What do you want?
Let's hide!
Let's follow him, Keisuke!
All right!
There he is.
All right,
let's check out that room.
All right!
Wait, Keisuke!
Huh?
D-Demons?
But I don't sense any bloodlust
coming from them.
That's not all...
It's almost as if
their life force is gone,
like they're just empty shells.
Also... look at how many there are.
So, did that boy do this
all by himself?
If that's the case...
What's his endgame?
Watch out!
Damn it!
Father!
I knew you were following me.
Damn it!
I couldn't sense him at all!
Hikari, could these be...?
Yeah. Seems like it.
The descendants of
the Goshikidori Family.
What an unexpected turn of events...
How do you know?!
Heard it from the higher-ups.
Sounds like they have
some questions for you.
They can understand me?
Are you both Demons?
Demons?
No.
We're Devils.
The chosen ones.
D-Devils?!
#31, #56, Seize him!
Not bad.
I guess...
I'll entertain you a bit.
Hey, come on...
We're not supposed to kill them.
Oh. My bad.
I can take on the Demons...
But I don't think I can win
against those Devils...
Well, what are you gonna do?
R-Run... Keisuke...
Get him!
I promise
I'll come back for you, Father.
Please hold on!
Damn it!
How am I going to rescue him?!
I can't do this on my own.
I need help.
Keisuke...
You actually have
an older half-brother.
His name is Keiji.
The day may come when
you'll fight side-by-side.
That's right!
I have an older brother!
But how do I find him?
Hey, look at this chicken!
It's crazy...
He blew that
Demon's head right off!
What the hell?
He's amazing!
Seems like he was spotted
in Midorino City yesterday.
That's gotta be...!
Midorino City is
three mountains away.
Him? I saw him by the station.
Oh. that man whore.
We just had a group date
with him the other day!
What a waste of time, huh?
I finally found you.
Big Brother...
EPISODE 8
NOT ALL FEATHERS HOLD A SONG
309, 310, 311...
312, 313, 314...
315, 316...
DUTY
- Even if I left...
- 317, 318, 319...
it wouldn't change anything.
320...
Eat up so you can grow up
big and strong!
323...32—!
Pops... I miss you so much.
Oh, you're awake!
I'm so glad!
You're okay now.
You should stay still,
your wounds aren't completely healed yet.
Th-That's right. I passed out.
Y-Y-You were the one who
nursed me back to health?!
I didn't do much,
I just stayed by your side.
S-S-Stayed by my side?!
Uh, th-thank you so much!
I-I 'm very grateful!
Th-Thank you so much!
Is this kid...
Not used to talking to women?
Well then...
- Th-Thank you so much!
- Um, uh...
No, no, no!
You should rest more!
I-I'm all right!
I-I'm totally feeling better!
But you really should stay
still and rest more.
Might be for the best...
What a funny guy!
B-Big Brother!
Damn it,
quit messing around.
First, you call me Big Brother...
Then you pass out for two days...
And now that you're awake,
you're horny?
You've got it all wrong, Keiji!
I was just...
I think you have me mixed up
with someone else.
I don't have a younger brother.
So, who the hell are you?!
M-My name is Keisuke.
I'm your younger half-brother.
Younger...
...half-brother?!
You better not be lying?
Do you have any proof?
We met once as kids.
He's...!
Wait!
This is for you, Sari.
Oh! You made this for me?
Well, does it look good on me?
Oh, uh... Yeah, not bad.
Thank you, dear.
Guess who?!
I wonder who it could be?
I don't know!
You sure got her!
Good job, Keiji!
Aw Dad!
You just gave me away!
You're the worst!
I love you so much, Dad!
I'm going for a walk, Mom!
Watch out for stray cats!
Go ahead, hop on my back!
That's Dad's voice!
Dad...!
Yay! Higher! Higher!
D-Dad?!
Who's that?
What's he doing with Dad?!
Hey there...
Are you from the neighborhood?
Do you wanna play?
You're that brat from that day...!
I didn't learn until much later
that we were related.
Brother, I came here
because I need to ask you a favor.
Father is being held hostage
by some Demons.
Will you help me save him?
I know that you've been
on a journey battling Demons.
Father told me.
How does he know?!
Our enemies are powerful.
I need your help, Brother.
I know this request may sound callous...
But I need to save Father,
no matter what.
Please, Brother!
I refuse.
W-Why?
He's your real father, isn't he?
I've got nothing to do with that man.
Dad!
Dad! Don't leave!
Dear...
Dad!
Not long after that,
my mother got sick from the heartbreak.
Mom, are you feeling better?
Yes, I'll be better any day now.
But then, one morning...
My mother was dead.
Leaving behind
her newborn child, Sarah.
My mother had protected
the last egg she had with my father.
She whittled away her life
incubating it.
Why, Mom?
Why would you do this
for that bastard's child?!
Mom!
I don't care that
he had another family.
But, my mother died
of a broken heart.
I'll never forgive him for that.
He killed my mother.
And I'll never forgive him.
I'm sorry you went through all of that.
But I don't see how
that's directly Father's fault.
What did you say?
How would you know?
How could the kid lovingly raised
by that piece of crap know anything?
"Piece of crap"?
If you don't like the word "crap..."
"garbage" works too.
You're free to think
what you want, Brother.
But to me, he's the father
and mentor that I respect.
I won't tolerate any more slander.
Not even from you, Brother.
Let's calm down a little, shall we?
Hey, Keiji!
He's a worthless son of a bitch.
He deserves to die.
Stop! Fighting is bad!
Wait, what?
No way...
Keiji's struggling?
Is this really
the limit of your strength?
Piece of—!
His movements are sloppy.
He's totally slow.
Let's call it, Brother.
There's no use in continuing.
Don't mess around.
I'm not stopping until
I beat you to a pulp.
Then I have no choice.
I'll put an end to this.
Hatsu!
Bou!
Ten!
Here I come...
Turbulent Strike!
H-He's...
Ridiculously strong!
K-Kei...
To think my brother was this weak.
Even if we teamed up,
we wouldn't stand
a chance against them.
And now...
I've offended my brother.
Damn it!
Even now, Father's life
is in danger...
I have no choice.
I can't give up!
Of course, he's in shock...
That must have been
the first time he's been beaten.
Piyoko?
Mister!
Eat this and feel better!
Don't want it.
Let's leave him alone right now.
Damn it...
I couldn't keep up
with his last move at all.
Not to mention...
It felt like my body
was exploding from the inside...
It was unbelievable...
That bastard!
I'll show him one day
by killing him!
Big Brother...
Bring it!
This time, I'll beat you to a pulp!
Got it?
That's not why I'm here!
I'm sorry about earlier.
I was wrong.
But I need to save our father,
no matter what!
If Father dies...
The world will fall into
the Demon's hands.
He's someone who can't die yet.
So please,
help me save him!
Please, Brother!
Can I ask you a question?
Miss E-Elizabeth!
What you just said...
What does it mean?
Well, Father and I have been
fighting to eradicate the Demons, too.
Why?
That's because...
It's the duty of the Goshikidori Family.
Our family and the Demons
have a long and intertwined history.
We're the only ones
who can stop the Demons.
Family? Duty to stop the Demons?
What is he talking about?
The same blood flows with you, Brother.
That's why I need your help, please!
Who cares.
It's got nothing to do with me.
Brother...
Hey...
Can you tell us everything
that has happened?
O-Of course.
Even with your strength,
you couldn't defeat them?
They must be plotting
something sinister
with all of those Demons
that they're controlling.
But to be honest,
it might be difficult defeating
those Devils.
But even so...
I can't forsake our Father.
I do not want to lose him.
No matter what.
So, by the way...
Do you know where
your father is being held?
Huh?! I-It's a warehouse
outside of town, in Akamori City.
About 50 kilometers west from here.
I-Is that one of those smartphones?
Oh, you know about them?
They're really handy!
M-Miss Elizabeth is so amazing!
Looks like there have been multiple
Demon sightings in Akamori City...
What?! Isn't this Demon...
Keiji!
Actually, I think we need to go
check this out ourselves.
Mo... Morio...?!
That kind Demon...
Why? Why is Morio...?
What's gotten into you, Morio?
Did Morio do this?
No way, Morio...
According to the internet,
Five Demons including Morio,
appeared all at once.
An hour later,
they disappeared without a trace.
Luckily,
no casualties were reported, but...
It seems this town has been
the target of multiple Demon attacks.
The abandoned factory
where the Devils are, is nearby.
They've got to be behind this—!
Demons!
Let's go!
Is that you, Morio?
Guess not.
I've fought this one
at the factory!
What?!
But I think
I've also seen this one before!
There's no mistake!
Stay back! He's mine!
Don't order me around!
I fight by my own will alone!
Stay down!
Hatsu!
Bou!
Don't kill him!
That Demon used to be
one of the good ones!
B-B-But!
We can't just sit here
and do nothing!
Leave this to me!
It's made out of a special material,
so it shouldn't break.
She's so talented!
Hey! Spill it!
Damn it, he's stubborn.
We know the Goshikidori Family's
goal is to eliminate us.
Was that silkie chicken
your only ally?
I...have nothing to say to you.
Damn it.
We'll see about that.
I-I have a report.
Huh?
What is it, Funakichi?
You didn't forget to
have those Demons
let off some steam, did you?
Y-Yes, about that...
#56 has been defeated.
Huh? By who?
The chicken
who escaped the other day
brought two others with him,
and they...
I knew there were others.
I bet they'll come here
sooner or later.
Hey, Mama?
If I catch those chickens,
will that make you proud?
Yes, Hikari.
That would make me very proud of you.
Father! I'm coming to save you!
Our opponents are countless Demons!
I can't depend on
Big Brother at all!
I have to give it my all,
or else—!
Next episode: Gone to the Birds
Miss Elizabeth?!
You're too amazing!
FAN ART CONTEST AWARDS